

Phattanothai Pukham

Software Developer

Personal Information

Nick Name	Fluke		
Military Status	Reservist		
Date of Availaility	Immediately		

I don't have much work experience. But I am ready to learn and develop. I'm the type of person who likes a challenge. easy to get along with I like to try new things and develop myself all the time.

I hope that we will have the opportunity to work together.

Contect

Tel	0635957755
Email	phattanothai.pukham@gmail.com
Address	96 Moo.6 Tambon
	Thanthong, Amphur Phan,
	Chiang Rai 57250
Github	https://github.com/phattanotai
Website	https://phattanothai-pukham-
	web.netlify.app

Skills

Graphic	Design	
Fair		
UX/UI D	esign	
Fair		
Coding		
	Fluent	
Databas	e	
	Good	
Server		
	Standard	
Research	1	
	Excellent	

EDUCATION

2012-2016 Bachelor of Science Program in Computer Science

Suan Sunandha Rajabhat University

GPA 3.21

2009-2016 Pali language

Wat Paknam Bhasicharoen

WORK EXPERIENCE

2022 - Present DRIVEN DIGTAL, WFH

Frontend Developer (Nuxtjs, Vuejs)

2022 - 2022 BE YOUR TECH, WFH

Software Developer (Nestjs, Nextjs, React,

Mysql, PHP)

2020 - 2022 OTEN INNOVATION, Chiang Mai

Full Stack Developer (Nextjs, Nuxtjs, Expressjs, Mongodb, React Native)

2019 - 2020 WORLD GPS TRACKER, Chiang Rai

Programmer (PHP, Angular, Expressjs, Ionic,

Postgresql, Mysql) http://wgtgps.net

2017 – 2019 Fort Mengraimaharaj Hospital, Chiang Rai

ABILITIES

Coding Nodejs, Javascript, Typescript, PHP, SQL, Python

Flask, Expressjs, Slim, Nestjs

Angular, Vuejs, React, Nextjs, Ionic, Nuxtjs, React Native, Bootstrap, Material Design, Tailwind CSS, Ant Design One Signal, Pusher, Selenium, Graphql, Apollo, Threejs

Sequelize, TypeORM, Mongoose

Google Map, Leaflet Map, Longdo Map

Integrate Api e.g. dlt, scg, cpf, Integrate gamebrand e.g.

sexy, pg, sbobet, sms, email, line api

Database Postgresql, Mysql, Sql Server, Mongodb, Redis, SQLite

Config Replication Master and Slave Server Postgis, Geo, Stored Procedure, Database trigger

Server Ubuntu, Window Server, Nginx, Kubernetes, Docker, Kong

Api Gateway, GCP, AWS

Tools Gitlab, Bitbucket, Github, Jira, Asana, Gather Town, Slack,

CircleCI, GitlabCI, Netlify, Cloudflare, Prometheus, Grafana,

gRPC, RabbitMQ

Research Microfrontend, Service Mesh Isito, ArgoCD, Jenkins, Apache

Kafka, Terraform, Ansible, SonarQube

Elasticsearch, Opensearch, LevelDB, Firebase

Flutter, Laravel, Spring Boot, .Net Core, FastAPI, Rust, Golang, Solidity, Wab3, Ethers.js, Kotlin, SwiftUI, Unity,

Facebook API, WebRTC, WASM